Lesson 40. Who's who? It has never been explained why university students seem to enjoy practical
第40课。谁是谁？从来没有解释过为什么大学生似乎享受实用
hoax: n.   骗局，戏弄
jokes more than else. Students specialize in a particular type of practical joke. The hoax,
开玩笑不仅仅是。学生专门研究特定类型的实用笑话。骗局，
deception: n.   欺骗，骗局
inviting the fire brigade to put out a non-existent fire is a crude form of deception which no.
邀请消防队发出不存在的火灾是一种欺骗的粗略形式，没有。
indulge: v.   使沉迷
Self-respecting student would ever indulge in. Students often create amusing situations which
自尊的学生会沉迷于。学生经常会创造出有趣的情况
pneumatic: adj. 气动的
are funny to everyone except the victims. When a student recently saw two workmen using a pneumatic
除了受害者以外，对所有人都很有趣。当一个学生最近看到两个工人使用气动
drill: n.   钻
drill outside his university, he immediately telephoned the police and informed them that two students
在大学外钻探，他立即给警察打电话，并告诉他们两个学生
pneumatic: adj. 气动的, drill: n.   钻
dressed up as workmen were. Terring up the road with a pneumatic drill. As soon as he had hung up,
像工人一样打扮。用气动钻头撕毁道路。一旦他挂断电话，
he went over to the workmen and told them that if a policeman ordered them to go away,
他去了工人，告诉他们，如果警察命令他们离开，
they were not take him seriously. He added that a student had dressed up as a policeman and was
他们没有认真对待他。他补充说，一个学生打扮成警察，当时
silly: adj. 无意义的，无聊的
playing all sorts of silly jokes on. People, both the police and the workmen were grateful to the
在玩各种愚蠢的笑话。人们，警察和工人都感谢
advance: adj. 预先的，事先获得的, archway: n.   拱形门楼
student for this piece of advance information. The student did in an archway nearby where he could
学生获取此预先信息。该学生在附近的拱门上做过
watch and hear everything that went on. Sure enough, a policeman arrived on the scene and
观看并听到发生的一切。果然，一名警察到达现场，
politely asked the workmen to go away. When he received a very rude reply from one of the workmen,
礼貌地要求工人离开。当他收到一位工人的非常粗鲁的答复时
he threatened to remove them by force. The workmen told him to do as he pleased and the policeman
他威胁要用武力将它们拆除。工人告诉他要按照他的意愿和警察做
remonstrate: v.   规劝，告诫
telephoned for help. Shortly afterwards, four more policemen arrived and remonstrated with the
打电话寻求帮助。此后不久，又有四名警察到达并与
pneumatic: adj. 气动的, drill: n.   钻
workmen. As the men refused to stop working, the police attempted to seize the pneumatic drill.
工人。当男子拒绝停止工作时，警察试图抓住气动演习。
The workmen struggled fiercely and one of them lost his temper. He threatened to call the police.
工人激烈地挣扎，其中一个失去了脾气。他威胁要报警。
ironically: adv. 讽刺地
At this, the police pointed out ironically that this would hardly be necessary as the men were
在这一点上，警察讽刺地指出，这几乎没有必要
already under. Arrest pretending to speak seriously. One of the workmen asked if he might make
已经下了。逮捕假装认真讲话。一个工人问他是否可以做
grant: v.   同意，准予
a telephone call before being taken to the station. Permission was granted and a policeman accompanied
打电话给车站之前。获得许可，并陪同一名警察
him to a pay phone. Only when he saw that the man was actually telephoning the police did he
他去打电话。只有当他看到该男子实际上打电话给警察时，他才
hoax: n.   骗局，戏弄
realize that they had all. Been the victims of a hoax.
意识到他们拥有全部。是骗局的受害者。